http://www.bouldereyesurgeons.com/patient-resources/online-privacy-policy/

Online Privacy Policy : Boulder Eye Surgeons
COVID-19 Update - Boulder Eye Surgeons has re-opened with new protocols aimed at keeping all of us safe. Click here for instructions for your next visit
P: (303) 444-3000F: (303) 444-3226 4745 Arapahoe Ave, Ste 100Boulder, CO 80303 M-F 8:30a-Noon & 1:00p-5:00pClosed on WeekendsHomeDoctorsDonald J. Keller, MDBrian E. Nichols, MD PhDKevin H. Cuevas, MDServicesCataractsCataract SurgeryFemtosecond Cataract SurgeryAstigmatismIntraocular Lens OptionsLaser For Secondary CataractsCorneaDry EyeMeibomian Gland DysfunctionGlaucomaVisual Field TestOptical Coherence TomographySelective Laser TrabeculoplastyEndoscopic CyclophotocaogulationPediatric EyesInfant VisionChildren & VisionAmblyopia (Lazy Eye)Eye Misalignment (Strabismus)Cataracts In ChildrenRetinoblastomaRetinopathy of PrematurityEye Glasses For ChildrenChildhood Reading ProblemsRetinaFlashes & FloatersLattice DegenerationDetachment & TearingMyopic DegenerationAge-Related Macular DegenerationDiabetic RetinopathyMacular EdemaOptical Coherence TomographyEyelidsBlepharitisStyes and ChalaziaEyelid TumorsPatient ResourcesEye Care Myths & FactsRefractive ErrorsHow To Insert Eye DropsLegal BlindnessEye SafetySports Eye InjuriesWorkplace Eye SafetyChildren’s Eye SafetyFirst Aid for EyesSurgery FAQsTestimonialsReferring ProvidersContact
HomeDoctorsDonald J. Keller, MDBrian E. Nichols, MD PhDKevin H. Cuevas, MDServicesCataractsCataract SurgeryFemtosecond Cataract SurgeryAstigmatismIntraocular Lens OptionsLaser For Secondary CataractsCorneaDry EyeMeibomian Gland DysfunctionGlaucomaVisual Field TestOptical Coherence TomographySelective Laser TrabeculoplastyEndoscopic CyclophotocaogulationPediatric EyesInfant VisionChildren & VisionAmblyopia (Lazy Eye)Eye Misalignment (Strabismus)Cataracts In ChildrenRetinoblastomaRetinopathy of PrematurityEye Glasses For ChildrenChildhood Reading ProblemsRetinaFlashes & FloatersLattice DegenerationDetachment & TearingMyopic DegenerationAge-Related Macular DegenerationDiabetic RetinopathyMacular EdemaOptical Coherence TomographyEyelidsBlepharitisStyes and ChalaziaEyelid TumorsPatient ResourcesEye Care Myths & FactsRefractive ErrorsHow To Insert Eye DropsLegal BlindnessEye SafetySports Eye InjuriesWorkplace Eye SafetyChildren’s Eye SafetyFirst Aid for EyesSurgery FAQsTestimonialsReferring ProvidersContact
Online Privacy PolicyHome > Patient Resources > Online Privacy PolicyENLARGE TEXT
A-  A  A+  A++  Effective: October 1, 2018 This notice discloses the privacy practices for www.bouldereyesurgeons.com. It applies only to information collected by this website. Collection of Information This website collects two types of information.  This includes:Information you voluntarily provide:Your nameYour email addressYour telephone number(s)Your mailing addressYour locationYour gender and other demographic dataPersonal health information (if you so choose) Information we or our agents collect automatically:Your IP addressYour operating systemYour device typeYour browser ID and other information related to how you interact with our website This information may be obtained through server log files, and additionally, through the use of cookies or other tracking systems. These cookies fall into different categories based on their purpose. Google Analytics gathers information allowing us to understand interactions with our websites and ultimately refine that experience to better serve you. You can customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated. Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. Some cookies are utilized to make advertisements presented to you more relevant to you and your interests. Such cookies are employed by Google Adwords, among other advertising platforms. Other tracking systems may utilize technologies like pixels, which are very small graphics files containing a unique identifier allowing us or our agents to see when someone has visited the site. Children Under Age of 13 Boulder Eye Surgeons does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website. How We Will Use Your Information Boulder Eye Surgeons is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not, under any circumstances, sell or rent it to anyone, or share it with anyone outside our organization, agents or website host and/or manager. We will use it only to respond to you about the reason you contacted us. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Unsubscribe or Opt-Out All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please use our contact form to send your unsubscribe request. Security We do not ask you to supply any credit card data or social security number via our website, and any personal health information you do supply is voluntary. You do not need to give details. We also protect your sensitive information offline. No-one is given access to it except employees or agents who need it to contact you or set up your file. View our HIPAA Privacy Policy. Be aware when you use any link we provide to leave our site. Read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites.Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement Boulder Eye Surgeons reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at http://www.bouldereyesurgeons.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Boulder Eye Surgeons decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner. Acceptance of Terms Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes. How to Contact Us If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email contact form, telephone number or mailing address. Email: contact form Telephone Number: (303) 444-3000Mailing Address: Boulder Eye Surgeons 4745 Arapahoe Ave, Suite 100 Boulder, CO 80303
Testimonials Previous page Quick LinksHomeOur DoctorsServicesTestimonialsContactSpecialtiesCataractsCorneaGlaucomaPediatric EyesContact UsP: (303) 444-3000F: (303) 444-3226 4745 Arapahoe Ave Suite 100 Boulder, CO 80303Get DirectionsCOPYRIGHT ©2018-2020 Boulder Eye Surgeons. All Rights Reserved.| Privacy Policy Design & Development by 2772 MARKETING Disclaimer: The information contained within this eye care website is not intended to be taken as medical advice. The information provided by Boulder Eye Surgeons is intended to provide general information regarding cataract eye surgery, laser eye surgery, glaucoma treatment, medical retina problems, and more for residents of Boulder, Longmont, Lafayette, Broomfield, Westminster, Thornton, and throughout the nearby areas of Colorado. This website is not intended for viewing or usage by European Union citizens. If you are interested in finding out more, please contact us today at (303) 444-3000 for a personal consultation.
